Atharva Danke

 $Boston, MA \mid 857.693.8526 \mid danke.a@northeastern.edu \mid https://www.linkedin.com/in/atharvadanke/ \mid https://github.com/Atharvaa97/Danke_Atharva_002762773$

SUMMARY

Software Engineer with 3 years of experience working on integration projects in the energy, retail, and finance domains. Possessing an in-depth understanding of service-oriented architecture and its related technologies like SOAP and REST. Proficient in developing and maintaining APIs using MuleSoft's Anypoint Platform and Studio.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- **Programming:** Mule 4, Java, HTML5, CSS3, SQL, and JavaScript
- CI/CD: Azure DevOps, GitHub, Bitbucket, and Jenkins
- Tools: Anypoint Studio, Eclipse, NetBeans, Postman, and Soap UI

MuleSoft Certified Developer- Level 1 (Mule 4), MuleSoft

Cloud services and Enterprise platforms: Microsoft Azure, Amazon Web Services, and Anypoint Platform

CERTIFICATIONS

AZ-900: Microsoft Azure Fundamentals, Microsoft

November 2021

May 2021

EDUCATION

Northeastern University, Boston, MA

Expected May 2024

Master of Science in Information Systems

St. Francis Institute of Technology, Mumbai, India

Bachelor of Engineering in Information Technology

May 2019

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Accenture, Mumbai, India

Application Development Analyst

November 2021 – August 2022

- Designed, built, and configured applications using Anypoint Platform and Studio to meet the business process and application requirements
- Worked on complex integrations, such as creating or retrieving ids from a source system database and transforming the data
 associated with that id into the format expected by the target client system, leveraging Salesforce connectors in MuleSoft
- Tested APIs using the Postman tool and used Bamboo to manage repositories and commit code and XL Deploy to deploy
 the code to various environments

Larsen & Toubro Infotech (LTI), Bangalore, India

August 2019 – October 2021

Software Engineer

- Migrated the client's existing legacy integration systems into a MuleSoft based API-led Anypoint platform by designing and developing APIs as per the API-led architecture using the Anypoint Platform, Studio, and Mule Runtime 4.3
- Generated API specifications using RAML in the Anypoint Platform and developed the business flows using connectors (Salesforce, SAP, Batch module, HTTP, MQ) and error handling in Anypoint Studio
- Performed data integration using DataWeave, unit testing using MUnit in the Anypoint Studio, and conducted testing of the APIs and interfaces using the Postman and SOAP UI tools
- Monitored the logs of the APIs in Splunk and created design documents that covered all aspects of the API design
- Used Azure DevOps and Bitbucket to manage repositories, commit code, and deploy it to various environments

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

St. Francis Institute of Technology, Mumbai, India MedTracker (Java, MySQL, and Android Studio)

July 2018 - March 2019

- Programmed an Android application that focuses on doctor-patient interaction. It allows the patients to classify the doctors
 according to the diseases that they specialize in and get their contact details
- Provided the functionality of setting multiple alarms to remind the patients to take their medicines as per the prescribed schedule, wherein the patients are prompted to take their medications either through an email or an application notification as chosen by the user in the settings tab